The walls gave the people
a century of peace and security.
The terror of being at their mercy
and the humiliation of being
trapped became a distant memory.
Until...
The battle for humanity's survival
began the moment the
Titans breached the wall.
After innumerable casualties
among soldiers and civilians alike,
it was learned that some Titans
were hiding among the humans.
Finally, five years after
the first wall fell,
humans succeeded in capturing one of
these disguised Titans: Annie Leonhart.
The existence of the Wall Titans
had been kept secret by the Wall Priests
whereof one of them
was questioned by Hange Zoë.
In the end, the priest still kept quiet.
Tell me, Pastor Nick...
Are all the walls made of Titans?
Nevertheless...
...the next threat to humanity
was already close at hand.
Hurry! Inform Commander Erwin!
Hurry!
There are Titans inside Wall Rose!
"12 hours earlier"
"South of Wall Sina"
Miche?
Tomas! Take three couriers and go!
I hear thuds! They sound like footsteps!
What are you talking about, Sasha?
It's the truth! I really hear footsteps!
Nanaba?
Everyone here?
Multiple Titans, 500 meters to the south.
They're coming right this way.
There's no time for you to gear up.
Take your horses and evacuate
all nearby homes and settlements.
Understood?
From... the south?
Has the wall been breached?!
As soon as the Titans reach the woods,
we'll split into teams
of recruits and soldiers alike,
and then simultaneously scatter
in each direction!
Avoid combat when possible
and focus on getting the word out!
Is anyone familiar with this region?!
M-Me!
And... so is Conny!
My village is to the south...
...where the Titans are coming from.
I can take you to the nearby
villages. After that...
...please let me visit mine.
All right.
You'll guide the southern team.
Yes, Sir!
The Titans have reached the woods!
Scatter!
Ride as fast as you can!
What?!
They all started sprinting!
Whoa! They're going to catch up!
Gelgar!
Take charge of the southern team!
Sir?!
He won't survive! I'll help!
No! We can't spare anyone else!
Have faith in him!
His skill is second only to Captain Levi!
Commander Pyxis!
Titans have been spotted!
Wall Rose has been breached!
Ugh. Those damn Titans never give us a break.
Can you go?
Not like there's much choice.
It was wise to have
Section Commander Miche watch the 104th.
I believe he can handle the situation.
Yes.
Let's hope so.
Four left.
No, it's time to go.
I've bought enough time.
Still...
...I am concerned about that Abnormal.
It's huge...
And I've never seen
a Titan covered in fur before.
Great! You're back!
I won't need to hold out until nightfall.
It went for the horse?!
You can't be serious!
Wait.
Huh? Didn't I just say to wait?
Tell me, what is that weapon called?
That thing on your waist that flies around.
I'm certain we speak the same language.
Perhaps you're simply too frightened.
Ah, well, I'll just take it back with me.
As long as we continue to fight...
...we are not beaten!
You can move now.
No! No!
Stop! Don't! No! No!
No!
So you can speak.
I must say, what a clever idea.
No! No!
Stop! No!
"Attack on Titan Season 2:
Roar of Awakening"
Oh, Eren.
Did you get into another fight?
Those jerks started it! They made fun of me!
So, I assume Mikasa had to
come to your rescue again?
Thanks.
Eren.
No matter how cruel someone is
or how much you hate them,
you can't always charge at them head-on!
You're a man!
Show some restraint!
You need to be there for Mikasa, too!
That's...
It fell.
You gotta be tired. Go get some sleep.
Sorry. I'm fine.
That thing's seen better days.
I'll get you a new one
if I see any in our supplies.
Eren! Mikasa!
This is really bad!
The Titans! They're inside Wall Rose!
"6 hours after the Titan spotting"
"South Team"
Conny, wait!
"6 hours after the Titan spotting"
"South Team"
Calm down!
There could be Titans anywhere!
Get back here, Conny!
This can't be...
Anyone?! Is anyone there?!
It's me! Conny!
I came back!
My house!
Dad...
Mom...
Sunny... Martin!
Please be okay!
Wel... come... home...
Conny! Get back!
Reiner? Did you hear that?
The Titan...
I don't know how, but...
Fall back, you two!
I'll scout the area!
Wait, it's...
It can't move?
Not with those legs...
"7 hours after the Titan spotting"
"Western Team"
"9 hours after the Titan spotting"
"Eastern defensive line"
"Trost District advance squad"
This is strange...
"9 hours after the Titan spotting"
"Trost District advance squad"
We still haven't found the hole.
"9 hours after the Titan spotting"
"Trost District advance squad"
We still haven't found the hole.
We haven't encountered any Titans, either.
"Stohess District"
What the hell does all this mean?
Damn it!
Would Titans break walls with Titans in them?
It's happened before.
They busted the wall into our city.
That was a gate.
Armin? What are you saying?
The thing about the walls...
There's no crevices between the rocks
or any signs of cracking.
We can't really tell how they're made.
So what if they're made
of hardened Titan skin?
Titans... in the wall...
Eren. Wear it right.
It's cold at night.
Sorry to keep ya!
Took longer to prepare than we thought.
Um...
Isn't this a priest from
the Order of the Walls?
Yeah. Nick and I are best buddies.
Right?
Don't let him bother you.
The whole makeup of this squad
doesn't make any sense.
Does it, Levi?
No, I think it might.
Erwin picked them out for a reason.
Open the gate!
The situation within Wall Rose is unclear.
But everything up until Ehrmich is safe.
We'll save time going through there.
Move out!
Yes, sir!
Take us out.
Huh? He knew?
There's Titans inside the walls
and he's known about it?!
Yes, though...
...he's kept his mouth shut this entire time.
But now he's coming with us
to witness the harsh reality.
Will his beliefs be strong enough
for him to stay silent?
Or will seeing it with his own eyes
make him question himself?
No, no, no, no! This is all backwards!
If there's something you
know, tell us about it!
Nothing's more important than
keeping humans from going extinct!
Eren, settle down.
You're still not fully healed.
There's more than one way to get answers.
I may be injured and useless right now,
but it doesn't take much to watch one man.
I'm hoping we can settle this
without blasting a hole in anyone.
Aren't you?
Threatening him doesn't work, Levi.
Believe me, I've tried.
It seems to me that this priest
is capable of sound judgment.
That's why I wonder...
What if the reason he doesn't talk
is because he knows something more
important than the fate of humanity?
"Ehrmich District"
Hey, keep moving.
You'll end up like a little lost kid.
Th-This is...
What did you expect you'd see?
This is what happens when the wall falls.
Mommy! Daddy!
Looks like someone was here recently.
Some bandits probably used it as a base.
It said "Ruins of Utgard Castle"
on one of the signs.
You, the Southern Team, met us
after having followed the wall
and couldn't find a hole anywhere.
Yeah. We'll have to check again tomorrow.
You rookies should try to get some rest.
Titans won't be roaming around at this hour,
but the rest of us will
take turns keeping watch.
We'll leave from here
four hours before daybreak.
Um...
If the wall weren't to be destroyed
the Titans... Where could
they be invading from?
I'm just saying, but...
Yeah... There's barely
any Titans around here.
If the wall was really broken, that is.
Finding the answer to that...
is our job for tomorrow.
Pastor Nick! Have you had a change of heart yet?
We don't have time for this!
You know, don't you?!
Will you talk, or won't you?!
Make up your mind already!
I cannot say anything.
The other believers are the same as I,
and that will never change.
Well thanks for nothing!
We're so grateful for all
the help you've been!
It's too great a decision
for a single person to make.
--The Order of the Walls must always adhere
to the sacred will we're bound to obey.
--This way.
--The Order of the Walls must always adhere
to the sacred will we're bound to obey.
-Sir! Thank you!
--The Order of the Walls must always adhere
to the sacred will we're bound to obey.
Whose will?
God or something?
I cannot say anything.
However,
I can inform you of a name, who under the
sacred will, we were instructed to monitor.
Monitor?
That person joined the Scout
Regiment as of this year.
Their name is...
Excuse me!
104th Cadet Corps!
Sasha Braus!
Her?
Who's that?
Um, this is for you, Section Commander.
You must find her at once.
Only she... She may know the truths
which even we cannot perceive.
That is all the information I can share.
The rest I leave in your hands.
If she's in the 104th, then she's deep
in the front lines right now.
Let's go!
We need to hurry!
Wait!
Ouch...
Sasha?!
What are you doing here?
Upon my arrival, I gave my report
to the Commander!
Afterwards, I was entrusted to deliver
this message to the Section Commander!
Message? Thank you. Good work.
So, who is this girl in the 104th?
She's the smallest one of us.
She's got long golden hair.
Um, and...
She's cute.
She's always hanging around Ymir.
"Ymir"?
Ymir? What are you doing?
Prowling at night, Reiner? Come to see me?
I thought I'd use this time to scavenge
for something that might fill my stomach.
This'll probably end up being my last meal.
This might do the trick.
Not that I like herring, but--
Is there any more?
Could I see it?
Go for it.
Canned food, huh?
What... are these letters?
I can't read any of it.
This says "herring" on it?
You... are... able to read this language?
Ymir...
You're...
Everyone, wake up!
Get to the tower! Quickly!
I couldn't see them in the darkness,
but then the moon...
Why? Why can they move?
It's been so long since the sun set!
What's going on here?
Hey! Look at that!
It's huge! What the hell is it? A Titan?
No, it's more like...
It's like a beast!
Right?
It's... climbing up for the wall!
Stand back, rookies.
Leave it to us.
It's time to show off our ODM gear.
Let's go!
Get your damn hands away from me!
You piece of shit!
Dumb-asses.
That was way too reckless!
Couldn't you have avoided that
without wasting your blades?
The door is bashed in!
The Titans broke through.
Go back down and form some sort of barricade.
We've all gotta do what we're trained to do.
Give it all we've got till we die!
Understand?
Got it!
I'll go see how far they've come through!
You guys grab boards or rods or whatever!
Bring everything you can carry!
Reiner!
Hey!
Wait up, Reiner! Hold on!
Who does he think he is,
always taking the most dangerous job?
Come on, man!
Yeah, that's a bad habit of his.
They're still below.
They're here!
Bring something, quick!
Reiner!
Reiner! Are you okay?!
Yeah!
Bertholdt, we're gonna survive and go home.
We're going back to our hometown for sure.
Right... Right!
We're going home!
Reiner! Bertholdt!
Out of the way!
Looks like that worked out, miraculously.
What now? Should I cut off its nape?
Don't even try.
You'll get hurt if it grabs you.
F-For now, let's retreat back upstairs.
There could be more
than just one that got inside.
Conny!
Reiner!
Uh, Reiner...
Don't tell me...
You're gonna jump out the window with it?!
I've got no other choice!
Wait!
If I can just slice open its jaw...
You're free!
Sorry... I'm sorry.
I think it's broken.
Yeah, just my luck.
I know.
Sorry...
All I've got is this dirty cloth.
Sorry.
No, it helps.
Gotta marry her.
Everyone understand?
Yes!
We're going our own ways now.
The rest is up to you.
Erwin may have thrown together your squad,
but everything's riding on you.
Eren.
Learn how to restrain yourself.
Don't succumb to rage
and lose sight of the goal.
We can't afford another mistake.
Yes, sir!
There's a tower nearby
where we can assess the wall.
It's in an abandoned castle to the southwest.
We'll ride to Utgard Castle.
That's mostly it for the big ones.
It's a good thing we have this tower.
Yeah, we might actually survive.
We'll go check on the recruits!
Okay.
What's that sound?
The horses!
Huh?
Again?!
What the hell is that sound?!
Lynne! Henning!
What was that?!
It's no use.
They both died instantly.
This can't be...
It's him! The one that
climbed up for the wall!
That Beast Titan did this!
A group of Titans approaching!
More than twice the number from earlier!
What'd you say?!
Their timing is too perfect,
like it's part of some strategy.
I get the feeling they've been
toying with us from the start.
This is bad! My gas is all but gone!
Did I get 'em?
This tower won't hold much longer.
I only have a small amount of gas left.
What about you?
No gas here, and I used up all of my blades.
Those blunt ones the last you have left?
Yeah...
How many did the four of us kill?
I don't know. I didn't
have the luxury to count.
You know what? I think I did
a pretty good job myself.
But the thing is...
I wish I could have a drink before I go.
Gelgar...
Sorry, Nanaba.
I must've hit my head...
I can't hold...
...any longer.
Gelgar!
No! No!
Father, stop!
Father! I'm sorry!
No!
Damn it all to hell!
Do we gotta wait here now until
the tower falls and we get eaten alive?
This sucks...
We'll be wiped out without
even finishing our mission.
I... want to keep fighting, too.
If only I had some sort of weapon,
then I could fight and die alongside them.
Christa... You're still
saying things like that?
Don't you dare use their deaths.
They didn't die so you'd have
an excuse to get yourself killed.
That's not... That's not what I...
You're not like Conny and the Scouts!
They don't want to die,
but you don't even care.
All you want to do is die in a way
that makes you seem like a hero.
Th-That's not...
Conny.
Give me that knife you had.
Huh? My knife?
Just hand it over.
Fine. Here.
Thanks.
What do you want it for?
Hmm?
Well, you see...
I'm going to fight with this.
Ymir... What are you planning?
Who knows? I don't even know myself.
Ymir...
Christa.
You've probably forgotten
all about it by now...
Christa...
Try to remember... that promise we made
training on that snowy mountain.
Promise me.
When I reveal my secret
to everyone, promise me.
Take back your old name and live.
Remember our promise, Christa.
Ymir! Wait!
Ymir!
Th-That Titan is...
...from that day...
Th-Thanks, Reiner.
Ow, it hurts! Reiner, my leg!
Reiner! That's enough!
Let her leg go! Her leg!
Hey!
S-Sorry.
No, you saved me.
Christa... Did you know?
That Ymir is a Titan?
I had no idea.
I was always so close to her, too.
How? How could this be?
In other words, she knew
some of the secrets of our world.
I wonder... What could be Ymir's goal?
Ymir!
She's--
Wh-What was that?
Is she worried about the tower falling?
She has to be.
If she wanted to,
Ymir could use this power
of hers to escape all on her own.
And yet, she's not doing that.
Don't you die, Ymir!
Don't pretend like you're good, you idiot!
You wanna go out in a blaze of glory?
Are you stupid?!
Live for yourself, goddammit!
If you're gonna die protecting
this tower, forget about it!
Tear it down!
Hey!
H-Hey! She's really tearing it down!
Keep it up, Ymir!
Want live...?
Grab me!
Titans again?
Hey, ugly! Go and finish the job!
Ymir!
This looks bad.
Ymir is...
This can't...
Christa!
Ymir, wait!
I still...
...want to talk to you!
I still--
I still haven't told you my real name!
Wait...
I still...
Christa. Everyone, get back.
We've got this.
Leave the rest to us.
Mikasa!
Have the others disperse and cover the area!
The rest of us will attack
where the Titans are gathering!
Got it!
Hey!
We don't need you to be a part of the attack!
Die!
I did it! My first kill!
You moron! I told you to stay back, Eren!
Right! I'm sorry!
Ouch...
Hey!
Eren!
You guys!
It can't be...
Ymir is...
Ymir...
My real name...
...is Historia.
Reiner! Grab on!
Right!
How's Ymir?
She's still in a coma.
Her bleeding has stopped, and we think
steam is coming out of her wounds.
For now, take her back to Trost
so she can get some proper medical care.
She's in your hands.
Understood.
Now then...
Damn, it hurts.
You all right, Reiner?
Not by a long shot.
A Titan nearly gnawed off my arm.
That was... pathetic.
I thought I was done for.
Even someone as strong as you
gets this way sometimes.
What are you talking about?
This is the second time for me!
Right, Armin?
Huh?
Remember the time I almost
got crushed in that Titan's hand?
Oh...
That makes twice I've nearly died.
At this rate, I'll be dead before I know it.
I picked this path on my own,
but being a soldier is rough.
It's like a soldier's spirit
breaks down before their body.
Though, until we plug up this wall,
there's no time to waste whining about it.
Yeah.
You two have been driven
far enough away from your hometown.
I'm thinking... this is where
we gotta draw the line.
Our hometown! Let's return!
Isn't it about time to go back?
Compared to all the trouble we've
been through, what's left to do is nothing!
That's right.
We're so close, it's just
another few steps till the end.
Huh?
What are you guys talking about?
Thanks, Mikasa.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine, but... Reiner got his arm bit
and Ymir is as you can see.
Who would've thought Ymir was a Titan, too?
Sasha.
Is everyone clear?
We'll deal with Ymir later.
For the time being, I want you to focus
on the mission to fix the wall.
Hannes?
It's the Garrison's advance squad.
They came to tell us where the hole is.
There's no hole anywhere!
Huh?
We spent all night looking for it...
...but at least between Trost and Krolva District,
there's nothing wrong with the wall.
What'd you say?
We bumped into soldiers from Krolva
and retraced our steps.
We haven't seen any Titans
the whole way here.
But... we know for sure there's Titans
on this side of the wall.
Did you actually look?
Are you sure you're not drunk?
I didn't drink!
Wait, why are all of you here anyways?
If there's no hole in the wall, so be it.
For now, we're falling
back to Trost District!
You guys aren't completely safe just yet.
Don't let your guard down.
There's nothing wrong with the wall?
What could this mean?
There's been nothing like this in five years.
Why is it all happening now?
This world is getting more
and more out of hand.
Eren.
Have a minute?
We need to talk.
What about?
Five years ago, we demolished the wall
and began our attack on humanity.
Oh no... What if there's a Titan
that dug a hole underneath the wall?
The hole will be hard to find in that case.
I'm the Armored Titan
and he's the Colossal Titan.
Right now, we need to focus
on getting Ymir back safely.
Even with our horses,
we still have to worry about Titans.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Why are you telling him, Reiner?
Our primary goal was to ensure
all of humanity was wiped out,
but now there's no need for that.
Uh...
Eren.
If you agree to come with us, we won't
have to destroy any more of the walls.
Understand?
Huh?
No, wait! I don't understand at all!
I'm saying... Why don't
you just come with us?
Hey! We're leaving!
What the hell?
And here I thought I had
enough to think about yesterday...
"12 hours earlier"
"Ehrmich District"
Eh?
What is it, Section Commander?
"Ehrmich District"
Oh, well...
I was finally able to get my hands on
the background report for Annie Leonhart.
According to this,
there were two others belonging
to the 104th Cadet Corps
who came from the same area as her.
And those two are...
...Reiner Braun... and Bertholdt Hoover.
Thanks to the chaos five years ago,
pretty much all of their family records are spotty or missing.
However...
During the long-range scouting formation,
their unit was given false information.
They were among those purposely told
that Eren was in the right wing.
The Female Titan attacked
from the right wing!
Huh? What does that mean?
That it's possible they passed on
that information to Annie...
Hey, hold on a minute, Armin.
Set aside Bertholdt, who doesn't say much.
Reiner is like everyone's big brother,
and he's not devious enough to deceive all of us--
I know, Eren.
By itself, that's not
enough to prove anything.
Everyone, listen up.
Supposing that we find Reiner or Bertholdt,
act in such a way as to not reveal any suspicions.
Of course, do not make any mention
of Annie Leonhart either.
Regardless if they're
Annie's accomplices or not,
we need to lead them
deep underground and confine them.
Does everyone understand?
Yes!
What the hell?
You're just tired, aren't you?
Right, Bertholdt?
You've been through so much,
it's making you crazy.
Y-Yeah.
Reiner's just really tired.
Besides, if you were really the Armored Titan
that killed so many people...
...why would you be asking me
this in the first place?
What did you think would happen?
That I'd nod and say "Sure, let's go"?
Oh, right.
That's right.
What the hell was I thinking?
Have I really gone crazy?
Come on, let's go.
I see...
That's it.
I've been here too long for my own good.
It's been three long years...
surrounded by nothing but idiots.
We were just kids... We didn't know anything.
If only I never knew that
there were people like this...
I...
...wouldn't have become...
...such a half-assed piece of shit!
It's too late now...
I don't know what's right anymore.
But the only choice for me now...
...is to face the consequences
of my actions...
...and as a warrior...
...fulfill my duty to the bitter end!
Reiner!
Are we doing it?! Now?! Right here?!
Yeah.
We settle this... right here, right now!
Eren!
Run!
Bertholdt!
Eren! Get out of there!
Eren!
I'm going to return to my hometown.
That's all I care about now.
Bertholdt...
Reiner...
You damn traitors!
Eren!
Everyone, jump away from the wall!
It got Ymir!
And somebody else, too!
All soldiers, prepare to attack!
We're taking down the Colossal Titan!
It's a threat to all of humanity!
Swarm the huge bastard!
Just like the reports said, he's slow!
It might be big, but that's it!
Compared to the Titans we
normally fight, this'll be easy!
Now's our chance! Slice up his neck!
Too hot!
Everyone, fall back!
He's trying to disappear again?
No, something is different.
The last time he vanished instantly,
but now, he's maintaining his form
and emitting heat like a furnace.
If he keeps protecting himself with steam...
We're unable to attack him with ODM gear!
Wh-What do we do?!
We can't do anything. We wait.
It's yet to be seen how long
he can keep his body burning, but...
...eventually he has to come out.
We wait for that moment to attack.
Listen up.
Forget about capturing them.
Kill 'em...
...and don't hesitate!
Armin... and squad one follow me!
We've got a date with the Armored Titan!
That did nothing!
Eren's attack didn't...
And my blades don't work either?!
What's worse, unlike Annie,
his whole body is hard!
Eren!
Hey, Reiner...
I don't know what kind of face
you're making right now, but...
You guys... You really are
the worst pieces of shit.
What the hell are you thinking?
I've never felt so revolted before.
Just remembering you and
your self-righteous face is making me sick.
It makes me want to vomit.
You... big damn pest!
It's time to exterminate you!
He threw the Armored Titan!
Wait... Isn't that...
...the technique Annie used?
It's working! I've got him now!
I still have a chance!
Think again!
Eren!
You're not getting away from this!
He did it!
Eren! Can you hear me?!
Run away! Get closer to the wall!
Their goal is to kidnap and take you away!
We've gotta escape and
prevent that from happening!
But, Armin, Reiner isn't going to
let us do as we please!
It's dangerous here! Get back, you two!
Huh?
Nice, Eren! Good call!
Mikasa!
Use these. It's the rest of my blades.
He's fast!
Shit!
Leg! His leg!
Don't stay on the ground! Eren!
Stand up!
Since I'll get knocked over anyways...
Bring it!
Gimme that neck!
You're mine!
I've got 'em! Now it's a battle of strength!
This freak...
Not enough!
Mikasa!
She cut him!
He can't fight back as much anymore!
You've got this!
Go for it, Eren!
Tear the head off his neck!
Pull the traitor outta there!
I can win!
Against Reiner... I can win!
Wh-What the--?
Heh, it's useless.
Keep at it! Don't let up!
He stopped...
But why there?
Be on your guard!
He's calling in Titans!
No other Titans spotted in the area!
What a useless struggle.
Try screaming for help with
your head ripped off, you idiot!
Look, he's tearing it off!
What's with the Armored Titan?
Why'd he scream like that?
Hey...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Above you! Look out!
"Trost District"
Commander.
Wake up, Commander Pyxis.
You'll get sick if you fall asleep here.
I can't believe you drank all this.
You're not young anymore.
And I'd rather not spend my days
changing your diapers.
Being cared for by a pretty lady
sounds all right to me.
So? What's the situation?
Patrols were sent out once the Titans
were gone from the 1st and 2nd defensive lines,
but any Titan sightings are few and far between.
Hmm...
If Hannes and the advance squad
followed the wall without problem,
they'll be returning any minute now.
Commander Pyxis.
Hmm?
Oh. If it isn't Erwin.
I hear you've captured
one of those troublesome mice.
Yes.
Unfortunately, we were one step behind.
Hmm...
But at least it will get those goons
in the interior thinking.
Maybe they'll reconsider how important
their stale beliefs and motives are to them.
Yes, it appears they have.
Look over there.
The Military Police have finally been
forced into an area with Titans.
Can you believe it?
I thought this was an emergency.
Yeah. And everyone's just sitting around here.
Hey, Levi. Where you hiding the Titans at?
Oh? You all seem so disappointed.
Sorry... A shame you couldn't fight Titans today.
If you're looking for another chance,
there's plenty of expeditions outside the walls.
How about we join forces
and face some Titans together?
A soldier from the front is here!
Inform Commander Pixis!
Mikasa?
Armin! Where's Eren?!
Mikasa, calm down!
You shouldn't be moving!
We don't know how badly you're injured!
Where is he?!
Eren was taken away.
Eren, he...
...he lost to the Armored Titan.
Ymir, too, by Bertholdt and Reiner.
It's been five hours since then.
Is anyone...
Is anyone chasing them?
No...
Why not?!
All the horses are on the other side of the wall.
In order to rescue Eren,
we have to wait for lifts to come so we can move the horses.
There's nothing we can do.
Section Commander Hange and
the other officers are too injured to move.
To even send out a small scouting party,
we're going to need more soldiers than this.
Soldiers with experience.
Understand?
Hey, Armin.
Why?
Why does Eren always go
somewhere far away from us?
Yeah, now that you mention it...
All I want... is to be at his side.
That's all I ask for...
Mikasa? So you're up, huh?
I bet you're hungry. Here, eat this.
Armin, catch.
As usual, field rations are all there is.
Hmm...
Taste neither good nor bad. Same as always.
Speaking of which,
this is the same as always, too.
Ever since the good old days, you two have been there
to clean up the mess of that brat.
That's what I call a lousy relationship. Sheesh.
It's a different time and a different place,
but you kids are doing the same thing you always have.
That brat isn't
even all that good at fighting.
But no matter if he's up against three or five,
he'll charge in all the same.
By the time Mikasa or soldiers showed up,
he'd been beaten into a pulp every time.
But you know...
I've never seen him win a fight before,
but I've never seen him get beat
and give up either.
Sometimes he's so tenacious
that even I think it's scary.
No matter how many times
he's knocked over, he gets back up.
That's the kinda guy he is.
You think he'll get taken away
without putting up a fight?
Nope. He'll keep resisting
as long as he has strength.
Even more so when he's up against just two.
He'll give 'em hell no matter who he's up against.
Until you or I show up to help.
That's how Eren's always been.
I loved those good old days.
If you ask Eren, he'd say those days
were nothing more than a false peace.
But for me, I'm more than happy
to be a drunk, useless soldier.
If it means getting back to
those plain, ordinary days...
...I'll do whatever I have to.
No matter how long it takes to get there.
I'm coming, too.
Without you three together again,
I can't bring back the good old days.
They're here!
Hey!
Isn't that...?
Commander Erwin!
And the Military Police!
You made it, Commander Erwin!
Is the situation the same?
Yes, sir!
Good.
Deploy the lifts!
Hange?!
Moblit...
G-Gimme a map.
It might be a long shot,
but there's a giant forest here.
We should head straight for it.
Why's that?
It's a gamble, but even if they have
the strength to change into Titans,
the other Titans outside
the wall might still be a threat.
Especially after all that fighting.
They might not be as bad off as Eren,
but I'm sure they're exhausted.
Which means...
they'll want to rest somewhere
where Titans are unable to reach them.
At least until nightfall when Titans can't move.
Oh, Eren...
You're awake?
What the hell?!
My arms!
I was the one who did that.
I kinda was in a hurry.
When I rushed to bite your nape,
I neglected to take your arms into account.
I see...
I... must've lost.
Eren, stop!
Hold your horses, Eren.
Take a good look around us.
We're in the giant forest within Wall Maria.
It's not even close to any of the walls.
In other words, we're
deep in Titan territory.
And then you've got these chumps.
Those dirty bastards.
They're the only ones with any ODM gear on.
Reiner's wearing gear he took from you.
So I don't think changing into a Titan
at this point is going to solve anything.
I realize that you're not
going to listen and do as I say.
But like Ymir was saying,
this place is swarming with Titans.
We could beat the shit out
of each other right now,
but when we're weak, the other Titans
would just come and eat us.
So until nightfall, when the Titans can't move,
we have no choice but to wait here.
Whether you try to run and escape from us...
...or don't and we take you away...
...either way, we wait for night.
Reiner.
You got any water?
If I don't get some soon,
I'm going to dry up and die.
Even if it's a matter of life and death,
there's nothing we can
do given our situation.
He's completely right...
This situation couldn't be any shittier.
Speaking of which...
Ever since the Titans showed
up yesterday morning,
we've been working our asses off.
With nothing to eat or drink
and not even a wink of sleep.
Fortunately, the wall
wasn't broken or anything.
So I think we deserve to
take a break for once.
We'll see about getting promoted later.
Reiner...
Actually, we've done plenty enough to deserve it.
I think we've performed outstandingly,
considering all we've been put through.
I know soldiers like us are expected
to fulfill their duties, but...
I think we've all earned it.
Reiner...
What in the world are you talking about?
What do you mean?
I'm not saying we go demand to be
promoted to captains or anything.
That's... not what I mean.
Oh, yeah. Where did you
all get that cannon from?
That really saved my ass.
It's a good thing Christa
helped me after that.
To be honest, I think she has a thing for me.
Hey...
Now that I think about it,
Christa has always treated me especially--
Hey!
You bastard... You've gotta be kidding me.
Huh?
What are you so angry about, Eren?
Did I... say something wrong?
If you want to die, just keep talking!
Hold up, Eren.
This isn't normal, no
matter how you look at it.
Isn't that right, Bertholdt?
If you know something,
quit with the silence and come out and say it.
Huh?
Reiner...
You're not... a soldier, remember?
You and I...
...we're warriors.
Reiner!
What are you doing?!
Hey...
Why...
...is Marco...
...getting eaten?
Right.
That's... how it is.
Huh?
What's he doing?
I thought it was strange.
Why would the guy who broke the wall
risk his life to save Conny?
Everything he does is contradictory,
but he doesn't realize it himself.
No...
Unable to bear the weight
of his sins, he convinced
himself he was a soldier protecting the wall
to maintain emotional balance
within his own heart.
And in the end, he believed it.
As a result, his heart was split
and his memories broken.
This must not be the first time
Reiner's talked and made no sense...
It's amazing, really.
For someone excessively honest like you to--
Enough!
Shut your mouth.
Sorry about that.
I might've pried too much.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Why are you pretending to be the victim here?
What's your deal?
I told you everything...
while you looked at me right in the eyes.
About the day my mother was eaten alive...
Isn't that right?
Thanks to the piece of wall you kicked
that went flying straight into my house,
my mother couldn't escape or run away.
What were you thinking?
What were you thinking when I told you?
Back then...
I felt sorry for you.
Oh...
I see...
You guys...
...are neither soldiers nor warriors.
You're just murderers.
You're psychotic mass-murderers
who've killed countless innocent people!
You don't think I know that?!
I don't need you to point that out to me!
Then don't pretend to have emotions
like you're one of us!
You guys aren't even human anymore!
It's you two who've turned
this world into a living hell!
Does that make you happy, murderers?!
What are you after by calling us murderers?!
Do you want us to regret it?
Do you want us to apologize?!
Would that give you satisfaction?
The people you thought
we were no longer exist!
If screaming will make you feel better,
then scream your damn head off!
That's right...
I'm still...
...too naïve.
I've...
...gotta do what I can.
Do what I can...
...to make you guys...
...suffer and die in the worst way possible.
You've got it coming.
You can't be serious.
Huh?
Quit it, Eren.
If you keep saying childish crap like that,
I've got no hope for you.
Huh?!
Hey, Reiner.
What's the deal with that monkey?
Monkey? What do you mean?
Hmm? You don't know?
That's surprising, given how much you two
stared at it with stars in your
eyes like two little brats.
That monkey...
What's "monkey"?
Just listen.
That monkey Beast Titan
is what caused this recent fiasco.
It made Titans rise up from within the wall.
I wonder if he was trying
to assess our strength.
That's where these guys are trying to get.
You... What do you know?!
Tell me everything!
Just wait. I've got circumstances of my own.
What the hell do you mean by that?!
Eren... if you think killing these two
will bring an end to everything...
...you're gravely mistaken.
Huh?!
Then who's the enemy?!
Enemy?
If I said that, the w--
Ymir!
Do you think there's any
future for this world?
If you know so much,
think about what you want to do.
It's not out of the question
for you to join our side.
And trust you?
Yeah, right. You two don't even trust me.
Wrong. We can trust you.
Because your one goal...
...is to protect Christa.
When it comes to her,
we should be able to trust one another.
If you come with us,
we can't guarantee your safety.
But if it's Christa we're talking about,
we might be able to do something for her.
Will it be your petty life...
or Christa's future?
It's up to you to decide.
There's no future for this world?
Why's that? What's "monkey"?
What's going on?
Hey!
Hey, say something! Who's the enemy?!
Ymir!
Who knows...
It's settled then.
Too bad, Eren.
You're kidding...
The Scouts... are already...
Dammit!
What's going on, Reiner?
Aren't we waiting until night?
Nope. We're leaving now.
Eren, don't try to resist.
Come on, don't get violent with me.
Look at the shape that I'm in.
Does it look like I can resist?
Please, gimme a break.
Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die!
I'll kill you! I'll slaughter you!
I'll kill you!
Hey. Why are we leaving already?
Ymir.
When you turned back into a human,
do you remember the person you ate?
No, I don't remember...
But if it was five years ago...
Was it one of your comrades?
I see...
Sorry... for not even remembering.
It's not your fault for forgetting.
It was the same for us, too.
I see...
Do you resent me for it?
I'm not sure... I... don't know.
You probably didn't want
to eat a human either...
How long were you wandering
outside the walls for?
About 60 years.
It was like... I was stuck in
a nightmare that would never  end.
A light?
Straight ahead in the forest! I saw a light!
It's the light that appears
when a Titan transforms!
Then we're just in time.
Soldiers, disperse!
We believe the enemy has already transformed!
Locate Eren and recover him!
Another one of the Military Police!
Battle is not our objective!
Prioritize recovery and retreat!
Phil! Round up the horses!
Yes, Sir!
First thing is to find the enemy
and let the others know!
They should be fleeing from the forest!
Break!
Eren.
Where are you?!
Is that the scream of a Titan?
It came from ahead!
You can't hide from me!
Wait!
This is Ymir!
She's the one they took! In Titan form!
Where's Eren?!
What about Reiner!? Bertholdt?!
So that's Ymir?
Did she turn into a Titan
and fight with Reiner?!
Did you get away from Reiner?!
Where are they?!
Tell us anything, Ymir!
Say something already!
Hey, ugly! We're in a hurry!
Something's not right.
Ymir!
Thank goodness!
You're all right!
Huh?
No...
She...
She ate Christa!
Don't just stand there! Chase her!
She's fast! We're losing her!
Why would Ymir do that?!
I can't be the only one who could've
guessed it would turn out this way!
Yeah! She's clearly hostile to us now!
Looks like she's cooperating with Reiner!
She lured us right in!
Here she comes, Reiner.
Right.
All squads! Let the Titans chase after you!
Follow my lead!
Erwin...
You demon! Are you trying
to use us as bait again?!
Eren's being taken away!
Don't stop!
Get on your horse and chase!
He's not fast enough to
escape! We'll catch up!
This time, I won't hesitate.
I'll kill them both, I swear!
No matter what it takes... I will!
Christa!
Ymir...
Ymir!
Chris--
No... Historia.
Sorry... for eating you... like that.
I bet... you're mad at me.
Ymir...
What is this? What are you doing?
We came here to rescue you and Er--
I don't need rescuing!
Just stay right there.
I'm following Reiner and Bertholdt now.
You, too. Come with me.
There's no future within the walls!
Listen to me, Historia...
Outside the walls isn't as bad as you think.
Especially... because there
won't be anyone saying that
you're better off not being born.
I'm pretty sure Titans won't be
saying that to me...
...because they'll be too
busy trying to eat me!
Everyone has at least one or two faults!
If you can just overlook that,
they're not so bad after all!
Ymir! Everything you're saying
and doing isn't making any sense!
Could it be... that Reiner and
Bertholdt threatened you?
Am I right, Ymir?!
I'll fight them with you,
so let me out of your hand!
I don't care if there's something
you can't tell me.
No matter what happens...
...I will always be your ally!
Reiner! Protect us!
I knew it! I'll have to kill Ymir first!
Wait, Mikasa!
Don't kill Ymir!
That all depends on Ymir!
What will it be? I'll kill everyone
that gets in my way, so choose!
No, wait!
Ymir will be killed unless she does
what Reiner and Bertholdt say!
She doesn't have a choice!
There's only so many lives
that I actually care about.
My enemies made
deciding that easy six years ago.
So... you're mistaken to seek
any compassion from me.
Because right now, I'm all out of time
and room in my heart to care.
Christa... do you pick
Eren or Ymir? Which is it?
Will you get in my way, too?!
Stop, Ymir!
Don't fight back! You'll die!
Don't move!
Quit it, Eren!
Don't struggle!
Good luck with that, Bertholdt.
It's impossible to get him to calm down.
He's the most irritating guy there is!
I know better than anyone!
I hate him as much as you do.
Hey... You're kidding, right?
This whole time...
you kept quiet and deceived us?
That's so cruel!
You guys! Tell us it's all a lie!
Bertholdt! Give him back!
Hey, hey, hey...
You think you can just keep running away?
That's not gonna happen!
For three years, didn't we
sleep under the same roof
as comrades through thick and thin?
But you...
To think you, the invader...
could sleep like a log...
...right next your victims!
Remember we talked
about surviving this together?
And that we'd grow old, and someday
we'd all go out for drinks together?
Was everything... all a lie?
Was it?!
You guys...
What were you guys thinking this whole time?
What's it even matter anymore?
Just focus on cutting open his neck.
They are enemies of humanity.
That's all there is to know.
--If you hesitate for a moment,
we won't be able to get Eren back.
--T-Tell me who!
--If you hesitate for a moment,
we won't be able to get Eren back.
--T-Tell me who!
Who the hell would want to kill people
by their own choice?!
Who the hell would like
doing this sort of thing?!
Do you think I wanted to do this?!
People hate and despise us...
We've done such terrible things,
we deserve to die.
Things we'll never be able to take back...
But... we just... couldn't
come to terms with our sins.
The only time we had some respite...
was when we pretended to be soldiers.
That's not a lie!
Conny! Jean! It's true we may have
deceived everyone, but it's not all a lie!
We really considered you comrades!
Neither of us have any
right to even apologize.
But... someone...
Please...
Someone, please...
Someone find us!
Bertholdt...
Give Eren back.
It's no use... I can't.
Someone has to be the one to do it.
Someone has to be the one
to stain their hands with blood.
You guys!
Get away from there!
I can't believe him...
What the hell is that Erwin thinking?
He's leading a horde of Titans this way!
You guys! Jump and get outta there!
All soldiers, disperse!
Get far away from the Titans!
Historia!
What's going on?
Is this hell?
No... but it will be!
All soldiers, charge!
The fate of humanity will be determined
in this very moment!
There is no future where humanity
can inhabit these lands without Eren!
We recover Eren and immediately retreat!
Give your hearts!
Mikasa!
What's happening out there?
What the hell's going on?
I can't move...
Unless I tear these Titans off me,
it'll only get worse.
In that case...
Brace yourself, Bertholdt!
A little more...
Just a little more!
It worked!
His hand's gone!
Now's our chance!
Hey, Mikasa?! Can't you
see all those Titans?!
Advance!
Commander Erwin!
Eren is just ahead!
Advance!
Right!
Mikasa!
You piece of shit!
Let her go!
Shit... This is all because I got caught.
Everyone's gonna die because of me.
Bertholdt!
Armin?!
What is it?
What do I have to abandon?
Is it my life?
Or something else?
Are you two okay with this?
Leaving behind your comrade
and returning home?
You're abandoning Annie?
You know where she's at?
Far north, deep underground in
the Utopia District... and being tortured.
It was her screams that taught us something.
That even with her body's healing,
you can never get rid of the pain.
They're taking special care
to ensure she doesn't die.
And as we speak,
they're not giving her body any rest.
They're torturing her
every way they know how.
You spawn of the devil!
I'll pulverize you!
All soldiers, retreat!
Damn that Reiner!
He's tossing Titans like a madman!
Eren! Mikasa!
Eren...
Eren!
Hannes!
What are the odds of this?!
Check it out, you two!
You just watch.
I'm about to avenge your mother
and butcher the shit out of this!
Hannes!
Give the old man backup!
Don't get in our way, you big sack of shit!
I did it.
My first kill.
Are you all right, Christa?!
Conny, that's wrong.
My name is Historia.
Hey, Ymir...
It's strange, really...
When I'm with you,
no matter how screwed up it gets...
...I'm not afraid!
Shit!
Don't, Mikasa! You're injured!
Untie my hands!
Hands?
Hurry up!
I've gotta be the one to do it!
Who said I was done with you?!
That one's... mine!
Eren!
Wait! We're trying to get you out of here!
It's time to settle the score!
Just watch!
Huh?!
Commander!
The Armored one is coming!
Jean!
Are you okay?!
Hold it together!
Shit!
What's wrong?!
Eren!
Right now...
...I've gotta become a Titan...
...or it's all for nothing!
Eren...
Nothing changed!
You haven't changed one bit, dammit!
You're still as useless as you ever were!
Nothing changed!
Mom...
I... can't...
I still... can't do anything at all.
Eren...
That's not true.
Listen...
...I need to tell you something.
You've always... been at my side.
Thank you.
You showed me... how to live with purpose.
And you...
You wrapped this scarf around me.
Thank you.
I'll wrap that around you...
as many times as you want.
Now and forever... As much as you want!
Why... are they...?
They're eating it?
Dunno what's going on, but now's our chance!
Let's hurry and run!
Right!
So that's how it is...
That's why Reiner was so desperate for Eren.
Which means, even inside the walls...
...there's a future.
This is the worst...
Why did the Coordinate have to fall into
the hands of the worst person imaginable?
We've gotta get it to us...
I can say... without a doubt...
...the one person in the world
I wouldn't want to have it...
...is you, Eren!
Get away from me!
You bastards! I'll kill you all!
Not good! Bertholdt!
I can't protect Bertholdt like this!
What? The Titans?
Eren!
Get on!
Armin!
Hurry!
Don't let this chance escape!
Full retreat!
Ymir!
Hey, ugly! What are you doing?!
We're heading back!
I sorry...
Huh?
Ymir! Where are you going?!
Leave her!
But Ymir is--
In that moment, I couldn't understand
the motivation behind Ymir's actions...
...but the Armored Titan
didn't pursue us any further.
Ymir...
Why did you come to us?
Oh, well...
If you hadn't come to bust up this wall...
...I would've never woken up
from that nightmare.
All I'm doing...
...is returning what I borrowed back then.
And...
It wasn't so bad, you know...
being a goddess for a while.
This is just our theory...
The fact that the Titans ignored us
and ran towards Reiner...
We think it was because of you.
It's a tough spot to be in, Eren.
Whether or not all those
people died for nothing...
...it all depends on you.
Yeah, you're absolutely right.
I've gotta do this.
I'll control the Titans.
I'll plug up Wall Maria.
I'll capture Reiner and make him pay.
That's what I've gotta do
to atone for all those lives lost.
Say again?
The Titans responsible for this incident...
were the citizens of Ragako?
In other words, the true
identity of Titans...
...is humans?
So... you're telling me...
...I've spent all this time and energy
running around killing people?
Is that right?
We don't... have proof yet.
Erwin.
Hey. Tell me.
The hell you smiling for?
It's nothing.
It's just...
...with this, we've taken
one more step towards the truth.
Just one step, huh?
We'll run out of people
before we learn the truth.
It's not worth the cost.
But it is a step towards the truth.
One day, we'll break it down.
This wall hiding the truth...
...will fall.
Wouldn't it be nice to take a walk
on some pure white sand,
gaze at the horizon
without living in fear?
Wouldn't it be sweet to watch the sun curve
down mid the waves
and taste the ocean spray
and realize we've been living
as slaves?
We've got to learn to get back, get back
but is it worth the price of our soul?
You know you had to kill her, kill her!
Oh my dirty hands, it never fades
And if we get out, get out
I'll think about the price of our soul
We've got to learn to live free, live free
We'll live a life without barricades
How long I haven't seen the light shine
through in my life?
Lost everything, family
Confusion on the way
Someone tries to talk to me
and signpost the righteous road
My animal inside
can now be tamed to go over
the wall
We've got to learn to get back, get back
but is it worth the price of our soul?
You know you had to kill her, kill her!
Oh my dirty hands, it never fades
And if we get out, get out
I'll think about the price of our soul
We've got to learn to live free, live free
We'll live a life without barricades
Sasha, I'll get Captain Levi chop you up
if you sneak some food out.
I won't. Probably...
Say what?
Hey! Did you guys wipe the dust and dirt
from your shoes properly before coming in?
Huh?
No, we didn't. Can't you see
all the stuff we're carrying?
Do you seriously think that attitude
will satisfy Captain Levi?
If I hadn't made your bed this morn--
Quit nagging! Who are you, my mom?!
We're back.
Wait, were you chopping firewood?
My body's getting dull.
You got grabbed by a Titan!
You shouldn't be moving yet!
I tried to stop her, but she won't listen.
I saw her doing sit-ups earlier.
How dare you, you peeping Tom!
Huh?
--Mikasa, you do know you're not
a wild animal, right?
--How does that constitute "peeping"?!
--Mikasa, you do know you're not
a wild animal, right?
It's almost like we're back in the Cadet Corps.
Yeah...
Why do you think we were chosen
for the new Levi Squad, though?
Protecting Eren and Historia
is more than an important mission.
Because we're talented, I assume.
What did you just put in your bag?
Nothing bread-related.
Why you!
Give it back.
Hey, focus! We gotta finish cleaning
before the Captain gets back!
Put back the bread.
--How many times have you done this now?
--What's this commotion about?
Our food expenses are precious!
Cut the crap, Potato Girl!
You should have had plenty of time...
Ackerman? Is that his last name?
I lived with him for a while when I was a kid.
Kenny!
"Starts July 2018!"