Re-Encoded By Henz
For Animeout
That's mean, Kacchan.
You're making him cry!
Stop, or I-I'll... make you regret it!
You trying to play hero...
even though you don't have a Quirk, Deku?
People are not created equal.
That was the reality of the world I realized at the young age of four.
And that was my first and last setback.
Izuku
Midoriya
Tatooin Station
That's one huge villain!
At 5 a.m, I felt like the silence was sinking into me, so I held my breath.
Shizukesa ga shimikomu youde iki wo tometa gozen goji
Biting my nails at emergency stairs. Which way leads to tomorrow?
Hijyokaidan de tume wo kamu Asu wa docchi da?
Never ending night and never ending rain
Keshite akenai yoru mo Furituzukete yamanai ame mo
do exist in this damn world.
Kono rokudemonai sekai niwa arundayo
It's nothing strange, though. I am just stuck in a slumber.
Sukoshi demo hen dewa naino Madoromi ni ashi wo torareteru
So I'm not blaming you.
Anata wo semeteiru wake ja naindayo
Daydreaming by yourself
Hitori kuusou ni asobu
Are you ashamed of the fantasy you had there?
Sokode omoiegaitakoto made hajirunokai?
It's all an entangled maze. Do you still want to go?
Karamiau meikyu meikyu Soredemo iku to iuno?
A small traveler plays a chime that signals the beginning.
Chiisaki tabibito ga kanaderu Hajimari no kane no ne
But the destination, I don't know it
Ikuatemo Don't know Don't know
Maybe you really are scared.
Honto wa kowainjyanaino?
But that will change with every step you take forward.
Fumidasu sono ippo ippo ga kaeteikerusa
It all began in Qingqing City, China
with news of the birth of a baby that gave off light.
Papa
Ever since, superpowers started popping up everywhere,
and time passed with no clear cause ever found.
Before we knew it, the extraordinary became ordinary,
and fiction became reality.
The world has become a society of superhumans
with about 80% of the world's population having some kind of "Quirk".
In this world, swirling with chaos,
the profession that you could only dream of came into the limelight.
And that profession is...
Oh, it's Death Arms!
Delivering justice with just the tremendous strength of his arms;
he's The Punching Hero!
Okay, everyone. It's dangerous here.
Stand back.
Backdraft, the rescue specialist is here too!
But man, turning into a monster is an amazing Quirk.
What did he do?
He stole someone's bag and went out of control when he was confronted.
He has a Quirk like that, and he's a bag snatcher?
I'm sorry, but the trains aren't...
Yes, I don't know what time I will make it to work.
Go for it, Kamui!
Get away!
Who's fighting?
Kamui Woods!
The young and talented rising star!
You asked, but then you gave a perfect rundown, kid.
You a fanboy?
Uh, well...
Illegal use of powers during rush hour, robbery, and battery...
You are evil itself.
Oh, here it comes!
Show us a flashy homerun, Tree-Man!
Preemptive...
Binding...
...Lacquered Chain Prison!
Canyon Cannon!
Huh?
Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy.
Today's my debut!
My name is Mount Lady.
A pleasure to make your ass-quaintance.
Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy.
Sh-She's getting the credit.
The rise of superpowers came with a rise in the crime rate.
While the country struggled to drastically reform its laws,
courageous people took matters into their own hands, like comic book heroes.
Guarding against paranormalities and defending against evil,
heroes were soon accepted by the public,
and it was established as an official occupation.
Based on their performance, they are paid by the government and gain renown from the masses.
Gigantification, huh?
Looks like a great crowd pleaser, and it's an amazing Quirk,
but her size would make it easy to cause collateral damage,
so does that limit its use?
No, she might be able adjust her size at will.
You're taking notes? Aiming to be a hero?
That's great! Good luck!
Thanks!
I'll do my best!
Episode
Aldera Junior High
Since this is your last year,
you should start thinking seriously about your future.
I'll now pass out printouts about your future plans.
But you guys...
are all planning to become heroes, right?
Yeah!
Yes, yes. You all have wonderful Quirks!
But using your powers at school is against the rules!
Sensei!
Don't lump me with these guys.
There's no way I'm gonna be stuck at the bottom with the rest of these losers!
Katsuki Bakugo
That was uncalled for, Katsuki!
Yeah, yeah!
Shut up, you bunch of nobodies!
Oh, if I remember correctly, Bakugo...
you want to go to U.A. High, right?
U.A.? That national-level school?
Their entrance exam was in the top 1% most difficult!
Their acceptance rate is always really low too!
That's exactly why you guys are nobodies!
I aced the mock test!
I'm the only one at this school who could possibly get into U.A.
I'll definitely surpass All Might and become the top hero!
My name'll be inscribed on the list of top earners!
Oh yeah, didn't Midoriya want to go to U.A. too?
Huh? Midoriya?!
You're kidding?!
You can't get into the hero course just by studying!
Th-They got rid of that rule!
There's just no precedent...
Yo, Deku!
Forget the rejects! You're Quirkless!
How can you even try to put yourself on my level?!
No, wait, Kacchan!
It's not like I'm trying to compete with you or anything!
Honest!
It's just that it's been my goal ever since I was little.
And well...
You never know until you try.
Whaddaya mean, until you try?!
Are you taking the test for fun?!
What the hell can someone like you achieve?
You're Quirkless!
12:02 PM, In the city
Thief!
Someone!
Catch me if you can!
Huh? There's no hero around.
Normally someone would come right away.
This guy is taking advantage of the chaos from this morning.
There are tons of people around who don't know how to use their Quirks.
There's no end to them.
There is an end.
Why, you ask?
Because I am here!
Hey, let's go to karaoke!
Sure, why not?
The incident from this morning is all over the Internet!
I wanna hurry home and write it in my notebook.
We're not done talking yet, Deku.
Hero Analysis for the Future
Katsuki, what's that?
Huh?
Hero Analysis for the Future
"Hero Analysis for the Future"?
Seriously?
Hero Analysis for the Future
Midoriya...
I-It's fine, isn't it?
Give it back!
Hero Analysis for the Future
How could you?
What?!
Most top heroes started making waves in their school days.
I want the notability of being the first student to make it into U.A. from this mediocre city junior high school.
I mean, I'm a perfectionist.
He's so petty.
So just to be clear,
don't apply to U.A., nerd.
Come on, you could at least try to talk back.
Let it go. He's pathetic.
Even now, he still can't face reality.
If you wanna be a hero that badly, there's a quick way to do it.
Believe that you'll be born with a Quirk in your next life and take a dive off the roof!
What?
Idiot!
If I really jumped, that would mean you instigated a suicide!
Think before you speak!
That's not fish food, stupid.
That's my notebook.
Stupid...
Stupid jackass...
Mom!
Mom, the computer!
Again?
Hurry up!
Jeez, you've probably added ten thousand views just by yourself, Izuku.
It's too scary for me to watch.
It was an old video.
A disaster that happened a long time ago.
The video showed the debut of a hero in the aftermath.
Can you see that?
He's already saved a hundred people!
That's unbelievable!
It hasn't even been ten minutes!
Absolutely unbelievable!
He's laughing!
Have no fear.
Why?
Because I am here.
He's so cool!
Once I get my Quirk, I wanna be like just like him!
You should probably give up.
Oh no.
Is something wrong with him after all?
Most of the other kindergartners' Quirks have already manifested.
But his still hasn't.
Excuse me, but you're fourth generation, aren't you?
May I ask about your Quirk?
Yes, of course.
I can pull small objects to me.
My husband can breathe fire.
Normally, by age four, he would have manifested
one of those Quirks or some combination of the two.
Early on, when the superpowers first started showing up, a research study was conducted and its results published.
It became common practice to see if the pinky toe was missing a joint.
When parts of the body aren't used, they're deemed unnecessary.
People who didn't have the joint were thought to be a newly evolved form.
You can see by looking at this x-ray that Izuku has two joints.
It's unusual to see that these days,
but that means he has no Quirk.
Can you see that?
He's already saved a hundred people!
That's unbelievable!
It hasn't even been ten minutes!
Absolutely unbelievable!
He's laughing!
Have no fear.
Why?
Because I am here.
Mom...
He saves everyone with a smile, no matter the danger.
He's such a cool hero.
Can I... be a hero too?
I'm sorry, Izuku!
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry!
No, that's not what I wanted you to say, Mom.
What I wanted you to say was...
I already resolved myself back then, didn't I?
That's right.
Don't worry about what other people think!
Hold your head high and move forward!
A villain!
A medium-sized invisibility cloak...
Relax.
I'm just going to take over your body.
Settle down.
It'll only hurt for about 45 seconds.
It'll be over soon.
I can't... breathe...
You can't grab hold of me; I'm fluid!
Thanks for your help.
You're my hero.
I never thought that guy would come to this city.
My body...
I have no strength...
I'm dying... Am I dying?
I'm dying...
Somebody!
Anybody!
Have no fear, young man.
Because I am here!
Texas Smash!
Wind pressure?!
All... Mi...
Hey!
He— Oh!
Great!
I'm glad you're okay!
Sorry 'bout getting you caught up in my villain roundup.
I don't usually make a mistake like this,
but I got too excited on my day off in a new place.
But you were a big help. Thanks!
I captured him safely!
The number one hero, All Might?
This is the real deal.
He looks completely different in person!
Oh, right! An a-autograph!
What can I...
My notebook!
He already did!
Th-Thank you very much!
It'll be an heirloom! A family treasure!
Okay!
Well, I need take this guy to the police.
See you again on the other side of the screen!
Wait, already?
Pros are always in battle against time and villains.
Wait...
There are still... things I want to ask.
Well then,
I'm counting on your continued support!
Wait.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Let go of me! Your fanaticism is too much!
If I... let go now... I'll... I'll die!
You're right.
I... have... a lot of things... I want to ask you!
Okay, okay!
I get it, so close your eyes and mouth!
Shit.
Th-That was scary.
Good grief.
If you talk to the people downstairs, I'm sure they'll let you down.
I seriously am outta time, so I really must go.
Wait! Um...
No!
I will not wait!
But...
You should probably give up.
I'm sorry, Izuku!
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry!
What the hell can someone like you achieve?
You're Quirkless!
Re-Encoded By Henz
For Animeout
That might be true.
But even so, I...
Even if I don't have a Quirk, can I become a hero?
Can even someone without a Quirk...
become someone like you?
My miraculous meeting with All Might...
At the time, I couldn't even imagine how much it would change my fate.
In the world surrounding me and my sullen self
Saenai boku to boku wo kakomu sekai de
No matter how I imagine it or try to grasp it, it's out of my reach.
Egaitemo tsukandemo madatookute
I was awoken by a dream that moves away as I approach it.
Nando chikazuitemo toozakatte iku yume de okita
The city filled with signs of daybreak lowers its voice.
Yoake no kehai de michita machi wa koe wo hisometeiru
Shakily, I am searching for my own raison d'etre in the dark.
Yureteiru boku wa sonzaiigi wo kurayami de sagashiteiru
In the world surrounding me and my sullen self
Saenai boku to boku wo kakomu sekai de
No matter how I imagine it or try to grasp it, it's out of my reach.
Egaitemo tsukandemo madatookute
What can I let go so that I can reach it?
Naniwosutereba sokoni tadoritsukeru?
No matter how many times I scream
Nandomo nandomo sakendemitemo
I am still myself.
Boku wa boku de shikanaikara
ゆめ
Whichever it is, dream or reality
Yume de arou to genjitsu darou to
I surely can go beyond.
Kitto koete ikeru
It's okay if I fall.
Korondatte ii
It's okay if I cry.
Naitatte ii
Because someday everything will
Itsuka sono subetega
bloom into a flower.
Hanani narukara
I am here for the next episode preview!
What? The villain I caught escaped?
It took a boy hostage and is going wild around town?
But I can't use my powers for much longer.
You're pathetic, All Might!
Is there another hero around?
Next time, "What It Takes to Be a Hero"!
Pros are always risking their lives!
Go beyond!
Next Time:
Plus Ultra!